mobico.my 2019-01-12

# Privacy Policy | Mobico.my

This information governs your use of the software application (please insert application name) ("Application") for mobile devices that was created by Macro Mobile Services Sdn. Bhd. In this information, "Macro Mobile Services Sdn. Bhd. "may also be referred as "We" or "Us". 

**Automatically Collected Information**

We respect the privacy rights of our users and we do not collect any personal information from your device or account. Anonymous usage statistics are collected and stored temporarily on Google Analytics servers for the sole purpose of improving our games and applications. We collect information about the number of times a certain level is started, the high score and similar metrics including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use, and information about the way you use the Application. The data we collect can in no way be associated with a specific user or device. 

**Customer Support**

When you ask for support, we will collect and store the contact information you provide and information about your inquiry or activity. We will also store the correspondence and any information contained within. 

**Payment Information**

All billing and financial information is processed by third-parties (e.g., Microsoft, Apple, Google). We do not process, store or share any billing information. 

**In-app Purchases**

Although the download of the Application may be offered for free, some additional content can be purchased for real money in-app. Such purchases do not always require the re-entry of credit card information because they may be made through an existing third-party account (such as an Microsoft, Google, Amazon or iTunes account). If you do not want to use this feature, turn off in-app purchases in your device's settings. To learn how to disable in-app purchases, refer to the device manufacturer. 

Additional content is offered "as is" and by making in-app purchases you, or anyone using your device and/or credentials, are responsible for any financial transactions and you agree that We will not be held responsible for any loss, material or otherwise. We reserve the right to deny refunding requests for in-app purchases in cases of negligence to the terms stated here in this agreement. 

**Third Party Access to Your Information**

We will share your information (in some cases personal information) with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. 

We may disclose User Provided and Automatically Collected Information: 

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process; 
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request;
  * with our trusted services providers who work on our behalf, do not have an independent use of the information we disclose to them, and have agreed to adhere to the rules set forth in this privacy statement; 
  * if we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of this information, as well as any choices you may have regarding this information; 
  * to advertisers and third party advertising networks and analytics companies as described in the section below. 

**Automatic Data Collection and Advertising**

We may work with analytics companies to help us understand how the Application is being used, such as the frequency and duration of usage. We work with advertisers and third party advertising networks, who need to know how you interact with advertising provided in the Application which helps us keep the cost of the Application free or low. Advertisers and advertising networks use some of the information collected by the Application and may also obtain anonymous information. 

**Data Retention Policy, Managing Your Information**

We will retain User Provided data for as long as you use the Application and for a reasonable time thereafter. We will retain Automatically Collected information for up to 24 months and thereafter may store it in aggregate. If you’d like us to delete User Provided Data that you have provided via the Application, please contact us at (please insert contact) and we will respond in a reasonable time. Please note that some or all of the User Provided Data may be required in order for the Application to function properly. 

**Privacy Policies of Linked Sites and Advertisers**

Our websites, applications and games may contain advertisements from companies other than abovementioned. We may link to their own websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. If you have any questions about how these other websites use your information, you should review their policies and contact them directly. 

**Security**

We are concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. We provide physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect information we process and maintain. For example, we limit access to this information to authorized employees and contractors who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our Application. Please be aware that, although we endeavour provide reasonable security for information we process and maintain, no security system can prevent all potential security breaches. 

**Changes**

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be made in this document. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes, as continued use is deemed approval of all changes. 

**Your Consent**

By using the Application, you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing," means using cookies on a computer/hand held device or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place in Malaysia. If you reside outside the Malaysia your information will be transferred, processed and stored there under Malaysia privacy standards.
